{
    "id": "55571b37f5c8483f8dd7f6cb6adaca66",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It has been years since I ……………… him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have seen",
                "saw"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81bddd2048c1482bb018e1377c442f1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old man has …………………. his best days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "seen",
                "shown"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cfc64be9878741149328bc9f4ebb77c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Marathi is ………………… in Maharashtra.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "spoke",
                "spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "284a29857b29428e9f7aa36d61bee516"
        },
        {
            "question": "At last his patience ………………… out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "worn",
                "wore"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6f10422820744d829160851bbf74f239"
        },
        {
            "question": "The inscription has ………………….. away in several places.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wore",
                "worn"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a4e2dced4ceb41e691c0ac71404aa151"
        },
        {
            "question": "Information technology has ………………… a long way since the 1970s.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "came"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b6144055e89449dea8f469b83354e2df"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… his books on the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "laid",
                "lain",
                "lied"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "91284eaed28944728503c9aa4535bdd5"
        },
        {
            "question": "A cloud ………………… across the moon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "swam",
                "swum"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "567db7bf08c74b2daf55312174476422"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old man was …………………. by a mad dog.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bitten",
                "bite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5bc07e5e858b4ad596ce11642adca1a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………. three hundred dollars for the pony.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bade",
                "bid"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b1c015c772924dbd923f0125b98b1e32"
        }
    ]
}